(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
待たれよ
Wait up!
あーっ！
Ah!
にっこにこ
Smiling!
あらあら
Ara ara
はふん？
Hahn?
にゃっ！
Nya!
眠たい
I'm sleepy
ちょこも眠たい
Choco is sleepy too
ちょこっ
Choco
待って待って待って待って！ お？
Wait, wait, wait, wait! Oh?
にゃー！
Nya!
はふん…
Hahn...
ごっち！
Gotchi!
やだやだやだやだ！
No, no, no, no!
どうも！ホロライブ2期生 悪魔で保健医の癒月ちょこです！
Hello! Hololive 2nd Gen demon nurse, Yuzuki Choco here!
お前何しとんじゃ！
What are you doing?!
うわー！
Whoa!
サンキュースバちゃん！センキューベリーマッチ！
Thank you Suba-chan! Thank you very much!
おら豚！登って！頑張って豚！
Hey pigs! Climb up! Good luck, pigs!
おら豚！こっちよこっち！
Hey pigs! This way, this way!
どっち？
Which way?
はいはいはい！なんだろう？
Yes, yes, yes! What is it?
何年やってると思ってるんですか？ ういー！
How many years do you think I've been doing this? Whew!
先生に向かってなんですかその言葉遣いは！
What's with that tone of voice towards your teacher!
友達じゃないんですよ？いいですか？癒月ちょこ先生だからね！
We're not friends, okay? Got it? It's Yuzuki Choco-sensei!
あ、やばい！うわー！
Oh, no! Whoa!
美味しかったのー！
It was delicious~!
あ、違う！ダメ！あー！
Ah, wait! No! Ah!
ちょこしかおらん
There's only Choco
中動いた！なんだあいつ！
Something moved inside! What was that?!
いらっしゃいませー！
Welcome!
どこ行きたいの？
Where do you want to go?
２期生に？
To the 2nd Gen?
なぁー！
Nyah!
おやすみー
Good night
あー…うしっ
Ah... yep
はぁ〜いい天気。保健室のベッドでお昼寝したーい。
Ah, such nice weather. I want to take a nap in the infirmary bed.
ちょこせんせーしょん
作詞・作曲・編曲：周防パトラ
Choco-sensation
Lyrics/Composition/Arrangement: Suo Patra
ずる休み
Taking a day off...
許されない
is not allowed.
保健室は神聖なの
The infirmary is sacred.
サボってる？
Skipping out?
今日だけね
Just for today.
誰も来なきゃ やる気出ない
If nobody comes, I've no motivation.
ちょこちょこせんせーしょん！ Yay！
Choco-choco sensation! Yay!
ちょこちょこせんせーしょん！
Choco-choco sensation!
このままじゃ私ダメみたい
At this rate, it looks like I'm no good.
さぁ起きなきゃ ふあ〜とお宝
Come on, I gotta wake up... a yawn is a treasure.
２回目のあくび おやすみなさい
The second yawn... Good night.
ごめんなさい
I'm sorry.
少しだけ寝かせて 先生モード
Let me sleep just a bit... Teacher mode:
シャットダウン
SHUT DOWN.
夢見るふわふわ
Dreaming fluffy dreams...
ずっとこうして眠りたい
...I want to keep sleeping like this forever.
ありがとう
Thank you.
ぽかぽか
So warm...
ちょっと休憩してるだけ
I'm just taking a little break.
油断大敵ね
Carefulness is key.
急に君が来るなんて
To think you'd come so suddenly.
ねえどこが悪いの？
Hey, what's bothering you?
何かを期待しているのかな
Are you expecting something, I wonder?
揺らぐ心
A wavering heart,
巡る感情
revolving emotions,
口どけ甘いせんせーしょん
a sweet-melting sensation.
癒されたい？
Want to be healed?
甘えていたい？
Want to be spoiled?
あざとくおちょこせんせーしょん
Cunningly, Choco-sensation!
君の視線
Your gaze,
君の体温
your body heat,
わかっても恋は量れない
I understand them, but love can't be measured.
元気なのに
Even though I'm fine,
溜息しちゃう
I end up sighing.
もしかして何かの病？
Could it be some kind of illness?
でもドキドキするまで動けないから
But I can't move until my heart thumps,
ときめき運んできてマイジュエル
so bring me some excitement, my jewel.
ずる休み
Taking a day off...
また来たの？
Did you come again?
保健室は神聖なの
The infirmary is sacred.
サボってた？
Were you skipping?
今日だけね
Just for today.
やっぱり君にいてほしい
Actually, I want you to be here.
明日は週末
Tomorrow is the weekend,
おやすみなんだよ
it's my day off.
家のみ 最高！
Drinking at home is the best!
引きこもり 最高！
Being a shut-in is the best!
もちろんノーメイク
Of course, no makeup.
暇になったら会いに行きます
If I get bored, I'll go see you.
さぁ全てを見せて
Now, show me everything.
ちゃんと診断できないじゃん
I can't diagnose you properly otherwise.
何を隠してるの？
What are you hiding?
鼓動のスピードは聞こえてるよ
I can hear the speed of your heartbeat.
見せて心
Show me your heart,
めくるシーツを
turning the sheets,
平静保てる天才っしょ？
it's a genius at staying calm, right?
愛されたい？
Want to be loved?
頼られたい？
Want to be relied on?
かまっておちょこせんせーしょん
Pay attention to me, Choco-sensation!
君の重み
Your weight,
君の匂い
your scent,
わかっても愛は量れない
I understand them, but love can't be measured.
大好きだから
Because I love you,
溜息しちゃう
I end up sighing.
やっぱりそれは恋の病
It really is a sickness called love.
でもドキドキするまで動けないから
But I can't move until my heart thumps,
ときめき運んできてマイジュエル
so bring me some excitement, my jewel.
揺らぐ心 巡る感情 どきどき 甘い セッション
Wavering heart, cycling emotions...
An heart-pounding, sweet session.
癒されたい 甘えていたい 頼ってよ ちょこ先生
I want to be healed, I want to be spoiled...
Rely on me, Choco-sensei!
君の視線 君の体温 分かっても 恋は測れない
Even if I know your gaze and your warmth,
I can't measure love.
元気なのに ダメージしちゃう もしかして もう手遅れ？
I'm fine, but I'm taking damage...
Maybe it's already too late?
でも どきどきするまで 動けないから
But I can't move until my heart thumps,
どきどき 運んできて 毎週で？
so bring that thumping every week?
ちょこちょこ センスえーしょん ヘイ！
Choco Choco Sensation Hey!
絶対君も 駄目にしたい
I definitely want to spoil you rotten too.
はいということで 癒月ちょこ生誕祭2026 始まりましたー！
Alright, Yuzuki Choco Birthday Festival 2026
has begun!
見て見て！一曲目から ちょこ 生まれ変わりましたー！
Look, look! Starting from the first song,
Choco has been reborn!
いや今日はね 原点回帰ということで ちょこの なんと 保健室ステージだの！
Well, today is about returning to my roots,
so it's Choco's... infirmary stage!
いやちょっと 保健室もちょっと生まれ変わって めちゃめちゃ可愛くなりましたー！
Yeah, the infirmary has also been reborn
and turned out super cute!
シチュエーションドラマとかできそうだよね
Looks like we could do situation dramas here, right?
今日は 生まれ変わった ニューちょこと 素敵な ゲスト様を いっぱい呼んで ライブをしていくんだけど
Today, I'll be performing with the reborn 'New
Choco' and many wonderful guests...
その前に みんなちょこのこと もっと見たいよね？
But before that, you all want to see more
of Choco, right?
あ でも まだダメだよ
Ah, but not just yet.
これから来る お二人に ちょこの撮影会をご依頼しちゃいましたー！
I've asked the two guests arriving now to
do a photoshoot of Choco!
それでは早速呼んでいきましょう ノエル様ー ラミィ様ー！
So, let's call them out right away!
Noel-sama! Lamy-sama!
ちょこ先生 お誕生日おめでとうー！
Choco-sensei, happy birthday!
ありがとうー！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
ということで 今回はこの可愛い両手に花で
So, with these two cuties by my side,
可愛いお二人に ちょこの撮影会をしていってもらおうと思うんですけど
I've asked them to hold a photoshoot for me...
まずは自己紹介よろしくお願いします！ ノエルちゃんから！
but first, please introduce yourselves!
Noel-chan, you start!
はい！こんまっする！ホロライブ三期生の白銀ノエルと！
Yes! Kon-massuru! Shirogane Noel from
Hololive's 3rd Generation!
はい！ホロライブ五期生の顔が肝臓 雪花ラミィです！
Yes! Yukihana Lamy from Hololive's 5th
Gen, whose face is her liver!
今日一日はよろしくお願いします！
Please take care of me today!
まあね ちょっと ちょこ先生の 本当に可愛くなったところを 団長 頑張って攻めていこうと思います！
Well, this Knight-commander will do her
best to 'attack' all those cute parts!
攻めちゃって 攻めちゃって！
Attack away, attack away!
ラミィも攻めるよね？
Lamy, you'll attack too, right?
ラミィもギリギリを攻めていきたいと思います！
Lamy's going to try and attack right to the limit!
撮影会やるなら ちょっとね この二人を呼ぶしかないかなーって思って 呼んじゃいました！
I thought if I'm doing a photoshoot, I just
had to call these two, so I did!
しかもしかも ちょっと後で この三人から なんと お知らせもあるみたいなので！
And what's more, it seems there's even an
announcement from the three of us later!
お知らせ何だ何だ！気になるー！
What's the announcement?! I'm curious!
撮影会の後で 皆様 楽しみにしててくださーい！
Everyone, please look forward to it
after the photoshoot!
それじゃあ早速 こちらで撮影会 よろしくお願いします！
Now then, let's start the photoshoot over here!
えっほ えっほ... うわー！なんかすごいとこ来たぞ！
Heave-ho, heave-ho...
Whoa! We've come to a crazy place!
すごーい！可愛い！
Wow! So cute!
可愛いでしょ 可愛いでしょ！
It's cute, right? It's cute, right?
撮影会は ちょこのここの 診察室でやりまーす！
We'll be doing the photoshoot here
in my examination room!
診察室だー ちょこ先生の診察室！ すげえ可愛い！
An examination room! Choco-sensei's
examination room! It's so cute!
いいですよ、いいですよ！いいですよ！
That's good, that's good! It's great!
え、でもさ、診察室だけどベッドは？ベッドどこ？あ…
Eh, but wait, this is an examination room,
but where's the bed? Where's the bed? Oh...
え？何かパネルもあれなんだけど…あれ使う？
Eh? There's also that panel over there...
Should we use that?
あ、ちょっとそこ、とんでもないものがあるけど…
え、これダメなの？
Ah, wait, there's something outrageous there...
Eh, is this not allowed?
そこはハートのメンゼンで使うの！
That's for the heart-shaped mosaic!
あ、何？そうなの？メンゼン？メンゼン？
Ah, what? Is that so? Mosaic? Mosaic?
そうちょっとね、ベッドとか、撮影会とか、
シチュエーションドラマとかやろうかなと…
Yeah, I'm thinking of doing a photo shoot or
a situation drama with a bed and stuff...
シチュエーションドラマ！とんでもないことをしようとしてる！
Situation drama! She's trying to do something outrageous!
本当だよ！
Seriously!
いえ、そうなんですよ。ま、でもそれはおいといて…
Yes, that's right. Well, putting that aside...
あ、おいとくんだ。
Oh, putting it aside.
ちょっと今回は二人に撮影をしてもらいたいので、まずは…
This time, I want you two to do the photography,
so first...
わかりました。撮りますよ。よいしょ。
Understood. We'll take the photos. Here we go.
ラミィ様には…
For Lamy-sama...
お！え、本格的な！すごい、カメラ来た！
Oh! Eh, a professional one! Amazing, a camera!
そしてノエル様にはこちらの、じゃん！
And for Noel-sama, this one, ta-da!
なんだい、これ？
What's this?
ちょこのギリギリを守るために特別に作られたモザイク棒です！
It's a mosaic stick specially made
to protect Choco's limits!
特別、すげー！チョコモザイク来た！
Special... incredible! Choco mosaic is here!
そう、ボタンでこのモザイクの粗さを変えれるらしい…
Yeah, apparently you can change the intensity
of the mosaic with a button...
今めっちゃ粗くなってるから…
It's really coarse right now...
あ、本当、薄くできる！本当だ！
Ah, really, it can be made thinner! It's true!
すげー、でもなんか粗いほうがむしろいいまであるなこれ。
Incredible, but the coarser one
might actually be better.
確かに。隠すや？これ大丈夫かな？
True. Hide it? Is this okay?
でも配信、ちょっと守りますよ。ちょこの配信を守ってください！
But the stream, I'll protect it.
Please protect Choco's stream!
頑張ります！頑張ります！
We'll do our best! We'll do our best!
それでは撮影会、スタート！
Now then, photo shoot, start!
イエーイ！まずはやっぱ全身。
Yay! First, the full body.
そうだね。そうだよね。普通にこうね、ちょっと…
Right. Yeah. Just normally like this, a bit...
ポーズ。いつものチョコ先の…こんな感じ？
Pose. Choco-sen's usual... like this?
ああ！美しい、こう…
Ah! Beautiful, this way...
美しい！
Beautiful!
ああ、いいねいいね。え、でもここちょっとまずいんじゃないの？ここ。
Ah, nice, nice. Eh, but isn't this
a bit dangerous? Here.
まずいかな？あら、逆に？え、逆に？
Is it dangerous? Oh, conversely? Eh, conversely?
ちょっと、結構ノリノリなんですけど！
Wait, she's actually really into it!
まずいかな？ちょっちょっちょっとね…
Is it dangerous? Wait, just a bit...
ちょっとここ揺れてめっちゃ…モザイクだ！モザイクが追いついてない！
Wait, it's shaking here so much...
It's mosaic! The mosaic can't keep up!
追いついてない！じゃ、ノエル様頑張って！頑張ります！
It can't keep up! Okay, Noel-sama, do your best!
I'll do my best!
こうやってね。あ、こういう感じでね。
Like this. Ah, in this way.
ちょっとどんどんどんどん…あ、ちょっとジャンプしてもらってみてもいいですか？
A bit more... Ah, could you try
jumping a little?
あ、ジャンプ確かに。すごいぷる…
Ah, jumping, definitely. It's so jiggly...
えい！よいしょ！あぶないあぶない！めっちゃあぶない！ダメダメ！あかんでしょう、これ！
Ei! There! Dangerous, dangerous!
Really dangerous! No, no! This is bad, right?!
アイアイオイ！あらあ…
Whoa whoa whoa! Oh my...
え、ちょっとせっかくだから椅子とかも座っちゃう？椅子？
Eh, wait, since we're at it, why not sit
on the chair? Chair?
うん、椅子ね、ここにありますね。はーい、椅子。よいしょ。
Yeah, the chair, it's here. Okay, chair. There we go.
おお、いいね！靴も可愛い！何かちょっと青っぽいんだね。
Oh, nice! The shoes are cute too!
They're kind of bluish.
あ、そう、ちょこね、そこが赤なの。
Ah, yeah, Choco's, the bottom part is red.
ええ！あ！ちょ、ちょ、ちょ、ま、ま、まずい！
Eh! Ah! Wai- wai- wai- wait, wait, this is dangerous!
ありがとうございます！そう、そこが赤なの、これが。
Thank you very much! Yeah, the bottom part is red, this.
ありがとうございます！そう。
Thank you very much! Yeah.
大丈夫？あ、でも何か見えてないからね。大丈夫です、大丈夫です。セーフですね。
Are you okay? Ah, but nothing's showing.
It's okay, it's okay. It's safe.
守ってます。チャンネル守ってます。
I'm protecting it. I'm protecting the channel.
いいじゃこうどんどんどんどん、上を見てもらって。
Good, let's keep going, look up please.
あ、いいね！あら可愛い！
Ah, nice! Oh, cute!
見えてる？見えてるよ、見えてるよ。うん。
Can you see? I can see, I can see. Yeah.
見えてる？あら可愛い！いいね！
Can you see? Oh, cute! Nice!
おお！いいね！あら可愛い！
Oh! Nice! Oh, cute!
え、ちなみにラミィさん、あれですよ。この椅子に座って先生ポーズも希望してましたけど。
Eh, by the way Lamy-san, about that.
She was also requesting the teacher pose...
そう、先生ポーズ撮ってほしい。先生ポーズって何だ？こんな感じ？
Yeah, I want you to do the teacher pose.
Teacher pose? Like this?
あ！いいですね、いいです。非常に。このモザイクいらないね、これは。
Ah! That's good, it's good. Extremely.
We don't need this mosaic for this.
非常に、非常に.本当にいらないの？隠そう？いや、わかんない、わかんない。
Extremely, extremely. Do we really not need it?
Should I hide it? No, I don't know...
ちょこ先の魅力が溢れすぎてて。いいですね！
Choco-sen's charm is overflowing.
It's great!
素晴らしい！え、じゃ団長もいいですか？何々？
Wonderful! Eh, can I also ask for something, Danchou?
What is it?
お尻フリフリちょっとしていただきたいんで.フリフリ。
I want you to wiggle your butt a little.
Wiggle wiggle.
えっと、そう後ろ向いてもらって。後ろ向いてもらって。
Um, yeah, turn around. Turn around please.
白衣越しだけど.フリフリ。あ、いいね！
It's through the lab coat, but... Wiggle wiggle.
Ah, nice!
白衣越しだが！あ、その下に！あ、ちょっと…
Through the lab coat! Ah, underneath that!
Ah, wait...
その下に！スカート結構際どよい。
Underneath that! The skirt is quite risky.
でもこれ、白衣、脱いでほしいんだけど、これ脱がないの？
But this lab coat, I want you to take it off,
but won't you take it off?
脱げるけど、メンゼンって言ってた。あ、メンゼンなら脱いでくれるんですね！
I can take it off, but they mentioned the mosaic.
Ah, so you'll take it off if there's a mosaic!
あーい！え、ガニ股…団長ガニ股好きなんで。
Yes! Eh, bow-legged... Danchou likes bow-legged poses.
うわあ！ガニ股さん！いいね！ガニ股助かる！
Whoa! Bow-legged! Nice! Bow-legged is a lifesaver!
ガニ股！これちょっとモザイクモザイク！
Bow-legged! This needs mosaic, mosaic!
ちょ、見えてるもんな.モザイクお願いします！モザイクがむしろここが？
Wait, it's showing. Mosaic please!
Is the mosaic actually here?
うわあ！逆にヤバい！ヤバいヤバいヤバい！
Whoa! It's dangerous in the opposite way!
Dangerous, dangerous!
ヤバいヤバい！可愛い！ふー！
Dangerous, dangerous! Cute! Phew!
どんどん行こうどんどん行こう.えっと…
Let's keep going, let's keep going. Um...
じゃ、ラストはやっぱアイドルだからさ、チョコ先、アイドル.飛び切りの可愛いアイドルお願いします。
Then, for the last one, since you're an idol,
Choco-sen, an exceptionally cute idol pose please.
あーい！え、可愛い！
Yes! Eh, cute!
いや これはあ いいねぇ です！
Oh, this is nice! It's great!
かわいい！
Cute!
ん〜まっ！
Mwuah!
いや アップいい 顔のアップいいいいねぇ
Close-up! Close-up of your face is great!
たまらんです
I can't get enough of it!
かわいい！
Cute!
オッケー！いっぱいいただいた！
Okay! I got a lot of photos!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いやちょっとね この続きはちょっとメン限でやらせていただきますので
Well, we'll be continuing the rest on the membership stream.
メン限ではちょっと歌も撮影会も
In membership, we have an after-live, photo session...
シチュドラもなんと2本やっちゃいます！
...and even two situation dramas!
楽しみだ〜！
We're looking forward to it!
ちなみにさ なんかタイトルとかあんの そのシチュエーションドラマって
By the way, are there titles for those situation dramas?
あ 今回のタイトルが…
The titles this time are...
『先生とベッドで特別バレンタイン』
'Special Valentine in Bed with Sensei'...
え！特別？！先生とベッドで？！
Special?! In bed with Sensei?!
ってタイトルと、あと…
...is one title. And the other is...
『診察室で甘い処方箋を』っていう
...'A Sweet Prescription in the Examination Room'!
あ〜あ〜甘い！診察室！
Ohhh! Sweet! Examination room!
最高すぎる！
That sounds too good!
目線もちょっとカメラマンさんをベッドに横たわらせて
For the perspective, I'll have the camera operator lie down on the bed...
ちょっとみんなが本当に見えるように
...so everyone can really feel like they're there.
そっちょこが覆いかぶさるようにいろんな画角で撮っていきたいと思います
I'll be leaning over you from different angles.
うぉ〜楽しみだ！
Whoa! We're looking forward to it!
ということでそろそろお時間が迫ってきたので
Well, it's about time.
ちょっとライブの方に戻りたいと思います！
Let's get back to the live performance!
そうだ！ライブだった！
That's right! It's a live concert!
急げ！急げ！
Hurry! Hurry!
はい！ということで！
Alright, then!
このあと2人それぞれちょっとデュエットしてもらうんだけど
Next, each of us will perform a duet...
最後に3人でも歌うので楽しみにしてて下さい！
...and finally, all three of us will sing together!
楽しみ！お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
それでは着替えに行きましょうか！
Now, let's go change!
お！これ？！すごい！
Wow! Is this it?!
カーテン！リボンもついてる。かわいい！
A curtain! It even has ribbons. So cute!
じゃあちょっとカーテンの裏でお着替え行ってきます！
Okay, we're going to change behind the curtain!
それでは聴いてください
Please listen to our next song.
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
どろどろ とろり べいっび
Melting, sticky, baby
とろけちゃって Catch me だーりん
Melting away, Catch me, darling
ぴゅあぴゅあ ここあ ふわり きゅるきゅる
Pure, pure, cocoa, fluffily, swirling, swirling
わんつー！
One, two!
なんか眠れない夜には お散歩
On nights when I can't sleep, I take a walk
特別パーティータイム
Special party time
2人きり(やったー)
Just the two of us (Yay!)
あの角 曲がれば
If you turn that corner
ベンチしかない公園だよ
It's a park with only benches
蒸し暑い 空気の中
In the humid air
迷い込むんだ
I get lost
コンビニ ちょっと寄り道(買い出し)
A little detour to the convenience store (shopping)
アイスじゃなくって、これがいい
Not ice cream, I want this
缶のお酒 ほろ酔い
Canned alcohol, feeling tipsy
ウインクで すとろんぐ！
Strong with a wink!
リキュールじゃ もう酔えない
Can't get drunk on liqueur anymore
ラブで潰して(お願い)
Crush me with love (Please)
お砂糖 ワンサマシマシで
Extra sugar, more and more
飲みやすさとかいらない
I don't need it to be easy to drink
灼熱でさ 溶かして
Melt me with scorching heat
ごくって飲んで
Gulp it down
クセのある私だからさ
Because I'm quirky
君が選ばれたサマーチョコレート
Because you were chosen, Summer Chocolate
どろどろ とろり べいっび
Melting, sticky, baby
とろけちゃって Catch me だーりん
Melting away, Catch me, darling
ぴゅあぴゅあ ここあ ふわり きゅるきゅる
Pure, pure, cocoa, fluffily, swirling, swirling
わんつー！
One, two!
ちょっと寂しい帰り道
A little lonely on the way home
フラフラ 特別ボーナスタイム
Dizzy, special bonus time
手をつなごう(にゃんにゃん)
Let's hold hands (Meow-meow)
大きめ Tシャツ
Oversized T-shirt
君に借りた ありがとうって
The one I borrowed from you, thank you
寝起きみたいにして
Like I just woke up
困らせたいんだ
I want to trouble you
コンビニ また寄っちゃって
Stopping by the convenience store again
楽しい もう一本だけ
Fun, just one more bottle
弱いやつ
Something weak
ふるふる 震える
Shaking, trembling
瞳に ベルベット
Velvet in your eyes
どろどろ とろり べいっび
Melting, dripping, baby
とろけちゃって Catch me だーりん
Melting away, catch me, darling
ぴゅあぴゅあ ここあ ふわり
Pure, pure, cocoa, fluffily
きゅるきゅる なんか眠れない夜には
Whirling, whirling, on a night I can't sleep
お散歩 特別パーティータイム
Taking a walk, special party time
2人きり (やったー)
Just the two of us (Yay!)
あの角 曲がれば
If we turn that corner...
ベンチしかない公園だよ
it's a park with only benches.
蒸し暑い 空気の中
In the sultry air...
迷い込むんだ
I get lost.
コンビニ ちょっと アイス買いに
Going to the convenience store to buy ice cream
(I need, I want, I love you...)
あー
Ah...
愛は伝えなきゃ届かない
Love won't reach unless you express it
恋してる チョコにここでチュッてして
To Choco who's in love, give me a kiss right here
夜空のグラスに キラキラこぼして
Spilling sparkles into the glass of the night sky
息もできないくらいに 踊って
Dancing so much that I can't even breathe
(だって だって だって)
(Because, because, because)
恋に溺れて
Drowning in love
君の熱で溶けたら
If I melt with your heat
そのまんまで食べてよ
Eat me just as I am
手にベトベトついちゃって
Getting all sticky on your hands
いっしょ いっしょ
Together, together
官能の酒 ほろ酔い
Intoxicating liquor, slightly tipsy
ウインクで ストロング
A strong wink
リキュールじゃ もう酔えない
I can't get drunk on liqueur anymore
ラブで尽くして お願い
Please, shower me with love
お砂糖はマシマシで
With extra, extra sugar
飲みやすさとかいらない
I don't need it to be easy to drink
灼熱でさ 溶かして
Melt me with scorching heat
ゴクって飲んで
And drink it all down
癖のある私だからさ
Because I'm a bit quirky
君に選ばれた
You chose me...
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
どろどろ とろり べいっび
Melting, dripping, baby
とろけちゃって Catch me だーりん
Melting away, catch me, darling
ぴゅあぴゅあ ここあ ふわり
Pure, pure, cocoa, fluffily
ぴゅるぴゅる
Whirling, whirling
One, Two!
What's up, Japan?
Can you hear me?
It's time to get down!
No money, no job, too much bunnies...
...but there's no reason to be down!
It's time to get up!
We have a hot new song!
That's from AKB48 to make you feel good!
Koi Suru Fortune Cookie!
Love Fortune Cookie!
So dance Japan crazy!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Koi Suru Fortune Cookie
あなたのことが好きなのに
Even though I like you
私にまるで興味ない
You're not interested in me at all
何度目かの失恋の準備
Preparing for my heart to be broken, again
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
まわりを見れば大勢の
If I look around, there are so many
可愛いコたちがいるんだもん
Cute girls here, aren't there?
地味な花は気づいてくれない
A plain flower like me, you won't notice
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
カフェテリア流れるMusic
The music playing in the cafeteria
ぼんやり聴いてたら
If I listen to it blankly
知らぬ間にリズムに合わせ
Without knowing, I start moving to the rhythm
つま先から動き出す
Starting from my toes
止まらない 今の気持ち
Can't stop, this feeling now
カモン カモン カモン カモン ベイビー
Come on, come on, come on, come on, baby
占ってよ
Tell my fortune
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Love fortune cookie
未来は そんな悪くないよ
The future won't be that bad
ヘイ! ヘイ! ヘイ!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
ツキを呼ぶには 笑顔を見せること
To bring luck, you have to show a smile
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
Heart fortune cookie
騒ぎだす 今日よりもしよう
Let's make more noise than today
ヘイ! ヘイ! ヘイ!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
人生捨てたもんじゃないよね
Life isn't so bad after all, right?
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
A surprising miracle will happen
あなたとどこかで愛し合える
I have a feeling we'll love each other...
予感
somewhere.
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Koisuru Fortune Cookie
あなたのことが好きなのに
I love you, and yet
私にまるで興味ない
You have no interest in me at all
何度も繰り返す失恋の準備
Preparing for yet another heartbreak
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
何度も試作した
I've made so many prototypes
横練習もした
and I've practiced too
夜明けになどなるな
Don't let the dawn come
大丈夫 自分史上
It's okay, because I'm the
一番可愛い私なんだから
cutest version of myself in history
君は私と結ばれます
You will be tied to me
結ばれる運命なのです
It is our destiny to be tied together
本命あげちゃう
I'll give you my true feelings
メルティン・ダーリン
Melting Darling
誰にも渡さない大戦争
A great war where I won't give you to anyone
ときめいちゃいます メルシー
My heart is fluttering, mercy
それじゃ手とか繋いじゃいな 内緒のデート
Then let's hold hands on our secret date
好き好きキス
Love, love, kiss
甘くていいの？
Is it okay if it's sweet?
好き好きはい！
Love, love, yes!
こういうのがいいっしょ？
This is what you want, right?
初恋なんだもん
Because it's my first love
絶対譲らない覚悟です
I'm determined not to give you up
本気なのですよ
I'm serious about this
目を見て言って
Look into my eyes and say it
君の気持ち
your feelings
ぴゅあら ぴゅあら ぴゅあら ぴゅあらぶ
Pure a, Pure a, Pure a, Pure a-love
はい！ということで、ちょこたち3人の新曲でした！
Yes! And that was the new song from the three of us!
イエーイ！新曲でした！
Yay! It was a new song!
改めまして、ノエル様、ラミィ様と一緒にですね
Once again, along with Noel-sama and Lamy-sama,
コラボ歌唱した「初恋大戦争」という新曲なんですけど
we performed our new collaboration song, 'Hatsukoi Daisensou'.
今回、作詞作曲を、めだんし様、
This time, the lyrics and music were by Medansy,
そして編曲を、後藤様にお願いいたしました！
and the arrangement was by Yoshike!
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you so much!
今回のテーマが、バレンタインの日に3人の可愛い女の子たちが
The theme this time is three cute girls on Valentine's Day,
一人の男の子を手に入れるためにバチバチにね、出し抜き合うみたいな...
sparring and trying to outwit each other to get one boy...
激甘なテーマ楽曲となっております！
It's an incredibly sweet theme song!
いいね！可愛い！
Nice! So cute!
いやもう3人の声が合わさって、めちゃめちゃアイドルソングになっているので、
With our three voices combined, it's truly an idol song,
ぜひぜひ皆様聴いてください！
so please, everyone, have a listen!
聴いてねー！
Give it a listen!
こちらの楽曲は、この後24時から、2月15日0時からで
This song will be available from 24:00 today, February 15th, at midnight,
各種音楽サイトにて配信されます！
on various music streaming sites!
やったー！聴ける！
Yay! We can listen to it!
そしてね、この配信後すぐに、この楽曲のMVが公開されます！
And right after this broadcast, the MV for this song will be released!
やったー！イエーイ！
Yay! Woo-hoo!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
ありがとう！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
大人なフリして。
Pretending to be an adult.
急に会いたいって
Suddenly you say you want to meet
いつものように準備してる
and I prepare as I always do
午前0時過ぎの終電で向かうって返した
I replied that I'd take the last train after midnight
やめておきなよって言われても
Even if I'm told to stop
大人なフリして。
Pretending to be an Adult
また会いに行く 会いたいから
I'll go see you again, because I want to see you
別別に落ち合う
We meet up separately
街の風は少し冷たい
The city wind is a bit cold
慣れないワイン 無理やり飲み干してしまっては
Gulping down wine I'm not used to...
ふらふら
...I'm dizzy
嫌われちゃったらどうしよう
What if you end up hating me?
下手にしちゃったらどうしよう
What if I mess up?
少しも残したくない
I don't want to leave even a little bit behind
ちょっと期待してね
Expect a little, okay?
ずっと見栄張ってね
Keep putting on a front, okay?
周りばかり気にして生きてる
Living while only caring about my surroundings
ちょっと憂鬱な夜も
Even on slightly depressing nights
なんか寂しくて
I feel somewhat lonely
ああ 本物の自分じゃない気がして
Ah, I feel like I'm not my true self
いつも大人なフリして
Always pretending to be an adult
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
Even though I'm not like that, I'm forcing it
マジのしないキスでも
Even a kiss that isn't serious
やっぱ一番嬉しくて
is still what makes me the happiest
取り繕った私は
The me who's putting on a facade
可愛いかな
is she cute?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, embrace me until I break
今にも切れそうな
A love connected by a thread
糸で繋がってる恋だね
that seems like it's about to break right now
私が諦めたらきっと
If I give up, surely
簡単に消えちゃうね
it'll disappear easily
引き留めるにはどうする
What should I do to hold you back?
あなただったらどうする
What would you do?
不器用すぎる指を絡めて
Intertwining our clumsy fingers
いつもチェックしてね
Always check, okay?
意気地なしでね
Being a coward, okay?
ほかのこと比べてばかりいた
I was always comparing myself to others
一番見てほしい
I want you to see me the most
目の前のあなたは
You, right in front of me
どこか違う景色見てる
are looking at a different landscape somewhere
いつも優しいフリして
Always pretending to be kind
そんなんじゃないのに笑って
Even though you're not like that, you laugh
近づけば近づくほど
The closer I get
遠く遠く感じて
the further and further away you feel
少しずつ離れて
Little by little, we drift apart
言葉枯れるよ
and the words wither away
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, embrace me until I forget
自分がもっと強ければ
If I were stronger
サヨナラを言えるのにな
I could say goodbye...
いつも大人なフリして
Always pretending to be an adult
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
Even though I'm not like that, I'm forcing it
ふと見せる優しさが
The kindness you suddenly show
ずっと忘れられなくて
I can never forget it
取り繕った私は
The me who's putting on a facade
可愛いかな
is she cute?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, embrace me until I break
突然こぼれだした
Suddenly, it started overflowing
私頑張ったよね
I worked hard, didn't I?
いつか振り向いてくれると
Thinking that someday you would look my way
思っていたもういいから
but it's fine now
取り繕った私は
The me who's putting on a facade
流れていく
flows away
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, embrace me until I forget
chocolate box
作詞・作曲：dezzy
Lyrics & Music: dezzy
なんかいつも眠そうだし
Somehow you always look sleepy
なんかいつもつまんなそうだし
Somehow you always look bored
なんかいつもやばそうだし
Somehow you always look like you're in trouble
なんかいつもスマホいじってるし
Somehow you're always on your phone
本当にテンション高いのに
Even though your mood is actually high
私といるとき低いし
it's low when you're with me
なんなん自分ありえなくない
What's with you, isn't that unbelievable?
嫌い大嫌いどうでもいい
Hate you, hate you, whatever
だったら僕も言うけどさ
Then I'll say it too
ちっちゃなことですぐ怒るし
Getting angry easily over small things
喧嘩したらすぐ泣き虫
Crying right after a fight
目処も返事もしてくれないし
You don't even give me a clue or a reply
そのわり飽き性やばい
Besides that, your boredom is terrible
どっか行こうとか言うし
Saying things like "let's go somewhere"
あーなんて罪深い人なんだ
Ah, what a sinful person you are
ちくしょうもう知らないぞ
Dammit, I don't know anymore
甘い甘い恋の魔法は
The sweet, sweet magic of love
ご愁傷様の秘密のチョコレート
Is the secret chocolate of my condolences
二人だけのデート
A date for just the two of us
…イノベーションを
...innovation,
切り分けて彩って食べちゃおうか
let's slice it, color it, and eat it up.
苦い苦い 愛の玉手箱
A bitter, bitter jewel box of love,
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
a mysterious chocolate with the taste of the future.
温めて混ぜたらきっと
If we warm it up and mix it, surely...
いつかお口に合う味になるの
it will one day become a taste that suits your palate.
ねぇねぇチョコいいかな？
Hey, hey, Choco, is this okay?
なんで？
Why?
さっきはあのねごめんね
About earlier, you know, I'm sorry.
何が？
About what?
いつもモヤってなるじゃん
You always get all moody, don't you?
それで
And so,
今日はこれを渡したくて
I wanted to give you this today.
言葉じゃ足りないからさ
Because words aren't enough.
だから
So,
受け取ってくれないかな
won't you please accept it?
何を？
What?
一緒にいてくれてありがとう
Thank you for being with me.
何だよそれ
What the heck is that?
あなたの優しさに ついつい甘えちゃった
I ended up depending on your kindness.
誰よりも近いから 素直になれない
Because we're closer than anyone, I can't be honest.
君の一生懸命さ ついつい忘れちゃう
I keep forgetting how hard you try.
誰よりも一番 大好きなのに
Even though I love you more than anyone else.
甘い甘い 夢の宝箱
A sweet, sweet treasure chest of dreams,
奇跡味の内緒のチョコレート
a secret chocolate with the taste of miracles.
二人だけのイノベーションを
Our very own innovation...
探し組み立てたら賑わおうか
let's search for it, build it, and have a party.
苦い苦い 日々の化粧箱
A bitter, bitter vanity case of daily life,
世界味の最初のチョコレート
the first chocolate with the taste of the world.
冷め切って割れないように
So that it doesn't get cold and break,
大事に包んで生涯の完成まで
wrap it carefully until the completion of a lifetime.
いつだって
Always,
やめる時も
even when we quit,
どんな時も
no matter when,
そう、ずっと
yes, forever.
健やかな時も
In health,
手を取って
take my hand,
違う二人を分かつまで
until we two are parted.
愛してる
I love you.
僕もそうさ
I do too.
そばにいて
Stay by my side.
そばにいる
I'm by your side.
なんて嘘かもよ
Just kidding, maybe.
ははっ、そうかい。僕も適当に言った
Haha, is that so? I was just talking nonsense too.
甘い甘い
Sweet, sweet,
苦い苦い
bitter, bitter.
甘い甘い 恋の魔法箱
A sweet, sweet magic box of love,
宇宙味の秘密のチョコレート
a secret chocolate with the taste of the universe.
二人だけのデコレーションを
Our very own decoration...
切り分けて彩って食べちゃおうか
let's slice it, color it, and eat it up.
苦い苦い 愛의 玉手箱
A bitter, bitter jewel box of love,
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
a mysterious chocolate with the taste of the future.
温めて混ぜたら絶対
If we warm it up and mix it, definitely...
いつか最高に幸せな味になるの
it will one day become the most happy taste.
せーので
One, two...
Thank you so much, see you next time!
ねえ、一つだけ 聞いていい？
Hey, can I ask you just one thing?
私のこと
About me...
会えるかな今日は
I wonder if I can see you today,
心が騒いで
my heart is racing.
好きと言いたくなった
I wanted to say 'I love you',
ときめきに踊る瞬間
the moment my heart leaps.
私のことなど
About me and such,
多分気にしていないのだけど
you probably don't care at all, but...
ここにいるんだよ
I'm right here,
私はささやく
I whisper.
意識が揺れ動く
My consciousness is swaying,
嫌われてないかな
I wonder if you hate me.
意気込みでとにかく
With all my determination, anyway,
あいさつだ！
I'll greet you!
やっと晴れたね ぱっと晴れたね
It's finally cleared up! It's suddenly bright!
そして元気になれるね
And we can be energetic, right?
おはようの代わりに
Instead of 'Good morning',
背中をたたいて さあ行くよ
slap my back and let's go!
やっと晴れたら ぱっと晴れたら
Once it finally clears up, once it's suddenly bright,
きっと元気な笑顔
surely a healthy smile...
なんだか今の
Somehow, this...
この気持ちが切なくなって
this feeling is becoming painful,
きたよ
it has come.
授業は上の空
In class, my head's in the clouds,
遠くを眺めた
I gazed into the distance.
恋って甘いもんじゃない
Love isn't just something sweet.
違うかも...
Maybe not...
ずっと半分
Always half
夢見るだけに
Just by dreaming
触って確かめなきゃだから
I have to touch and make sure, so...
動き出そうよ　自分らしくね
Let's start moving, in our own way
楽しく生きるの
Living happily...
毎日が奇跡
every day is a miracle.
言わずに悔やむより勇気出そう
Let's show courage rather than regretting in silence.
ずっと前から　うんとうんと前から
For a long time, for a very, very long time...
聞いてみたくて待ってた
I've wanted to ask and I've been waiting.
私から最初に伝えてしまえ
I'll be the first to tell you,
「大好きです！」
"I love you!"
ずっと前だよ　うんとうんと前だよ
It's been a long time, a very, very long time...
聞いたことに答えて
please answer what I asked.
どんな風に感じてるの
How are you feeling?
全部見せてよ
Show me everything.
楽しく生きるの
Living happily...
毎日が奇跡
every day is a miracle.
本当は不安でも勇気出そう
Even if I'm actually anxious, let's show courage.
ずっと前から　うんとうんと前から
For a long time, for a very, very long time...
聞いてみたくて待ってた
I've wanted to ask and I've been waiting.
私から最初に伝えてしまえ
I'll be the first to tell you,
「大好きです！」
"I love you!"
ずっと前だよ　うんとうんと前だよ
It's been a long time, a very, very long time...
聞いたことに答えて
please answer what I asked.
どんな風に感じてるの
How are you feeling?
全部見せてよ
Show me everything.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love,
光の矢　胸を刺す
an arrow of light pierces my chest.
君をわかりたいんだよ
I want to understand you.
「ねぇ、
"Hey,
教えて」
tell me."
すれ違う言葉にちょっとだけの後悔
A little regret in passing words,
涙こぼれて
tears spill out.
忙しい感情　鼓動にリンクする
Busy emotions link to my heartbeat,
チューニング確かめたいんだ
I want to confirm the tuning.
目的ばかりにとらわれて
Caught up only in my goals,
大事なものが霞んで逃げて
important things get blurred and run away,
今日もリスタート
starting over again today.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love,
光の矢　胸を刺す
an arrow of light pierces my chest.
全部わかりたいんだよ
I want to find out everything.
「ねぇ、
"Hey,
聞かせて」
let me hear it."
たった１ミリが遠くて
Even just one millimeter feels far,
駆け抜けた日々に
in the days we ran through.
忘れない　忘れられない
I won't forget, I can't forget
輝く１ページ
that one shining page.
お似合いの二人に何だか複雑な
I feel somewhat complicated about the two of you,
気持ちがいるよ
being such a good match.
初めての感情　鼓動にリンクする
First-time emotions link to my heartbeat,
体温計　壊ればいい
I wish the thermometer would just break.
…ちゃったかな
...I might have fallen?
自分のこと分からないまま
Without even knowing myself,
あの子にアドバイスまでしちゃって
I even gave that girl advice.
胸が痛いや
My heart aches.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love,
光の矢 胸を刺す
an arrow of light strikes my chest.
気付いたこの想いはもう
These feelings I've realized are already...
遅いの
too late.
あの子の方が可愛いの
She is cuter than I am.
知ってるよ だけど
I know that, but...
うまくいかないでなんてね
I hope things don't go well... just kidding.
逃げ出したいくせに
Even though I want to run away.
「バカ」
"Stupid."
君のこと全部わかりたいって思っちゃう
I find myself wanting to understand you completely.
これが恋だって初めて気づいたの
I realized for the first time that this is love.
絶対振り向いてほしい
I definitely want you to look my way.
遅かったけど 諦めたくない
It was late, but I don't want to give up.
だって好きだから
Because I love you.
春に咲いた花が恋をした
A flower that bloomed in spring fell in love.
花は必死に上を向いて笑った
The flower desperately looked up and smiled.
青い夏の蕾も恋をした
A blue summer bud also fell in love.
咲かない花と火薬の匂い
An unbloomed flower and the smell of gunpowder.
本当の気持ち言葉にして
Putting my true feelings into words,
大事なこと話せたら
if I could talk about what's important,
今日もリスタート
today is another restart.
鈍感な君だから
Because you're so dense,
口に出して言わなきゃ
I have to say it out loud.
今君に伝えるよ ねえ
I'll tell you now, hey...
「好きです」
"I love you."
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love,
光の矢 胸を刺す
an arrow of light strikes my chest.
全部わかりたいんだよ
I want to understand everything.
ねえ 聞かせて
Hey, tell me.
たぐり寄せてもう0センチ
Pulling you closer, now zero centimeters away.
駆け抜けた日々に
Through the days we ran through,
忘れない 忘れられない
I won't forget, I can't forget
輝く1ページ
this shining page.
はい！ということで
Alright! And with that,
ここまではアキ様、ロボ子
Aki-sama and Roboco,
ござるにふーたんと一緒に
along with Gozaru and Fuutan,
歌わせていただきました！
performed these songs with me!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
さてさて
Now then,
ここからはなんと重大告知が
from here, I have some
２つあります！
two major announcements!
まず１つ目がこちら！どどん！
First, here's the first one! *Drumroll*
癒月ちょこ誕生日記念
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration
2026グッズ！
2026 Merchandise!
それではちょっと詳しくご紹介していきたいと思います。
Now, I'd like to introduce them in more detail.
まずはこちら！
First is this!
ちょこのクッション！
Choco's Cushion!
いやこれね、ちょこの誕生日といえば
Well, you know, speaking of Choco's birthday,
毎年成瀬先生ありがとうございますということで
saying thank you to Naruse-sensei every year,
今年も成瀬先生にめちゃめちゃ素敵なイラスト描き下ろしていただきました！
Naruse-sensei has drawn another incredibly wonderful illustration for us this year!
今回のテーマはバレンタインということで
This time the theme is Valentine's,
チョコメイトを抱きながら
so while holding a Chocomate,
今回はチョコレート風のクッションにしてみました！
we made it into a chocolate-style cushion!
可愛いでしょ？
It's cute, right?
サイズ感がちょうど枕くらいになってるので
The size is just about right for a pillow,
お昼寝の時とか仮眠用に
so for a nap or a rest,
すやっとできる感じで使えちゃいます！
you can use it to sleep soundly!
そして続いてはこちら！
And next is this!
そして、重大告知、２つ目は、こちら！
And now, for the second major announcement... this!
……ねえ、ちょこ
...Hey, Choco.
もう二度と会えないの？
Will I never see you again?
不思議ね、キミの言葉を聞くと
It's strange, when I hear your words,
なんだか元気が出てきちゃう
I somehow start to feel better.
……ちょこのこと、もう少しだけ知りたいな
...I want to know a little bit more about Choco.
……ちょこのこと、もっともっと、大好きになってほしい。
...I want you to love Choco more and more.
もう一度、会いたいよ。
I want to see you once more.
この想いも、孤独な気持ちも……
These feelings, and this loneliness too...
全部、食べてあげるわ。
I will eat them all up.
ちょこは小悪魔なんだから。
Because Choco is a little devil, after all.
ねえ、もしよければキミに……
Hey, if you'd like...
ちょこの思い出話、聞いてほしいの。
I want you to hear Choco's stories.
「The Beginning」
The Beginning
12ヶ月連続オリジナル楽曲リリース＆連動ボイスドラマプロジェクトスタート
12-month original song release & linked voice drama project start
はい！というわけで、癒月ちょこ、12ヶ月連続オリ曲リリースが決定しました！
Yes! So, it's been decided that Yuzuki Choco will release original songs for 12 consecutive months!
あー！
Ah!
しかもこちら
And what's more,
なんとオリ曲に
believe it or not, with these original songs,
ストーリー連動のボイスドラマが
voice dramas linked to the story...
一緒にリリースされます！
...will be released at the same time!
いや、こちらね
Well, you see,
第1話から12話まで
from episodes 1 through 12,
1曲ずつに連動して
linked to each individual song,
ボイスドラマもあるので
there are voice dramas too,
ぜひぜひ楽しみにしててください！
so please, please look forward to them!
そして、今回はね
And today,
その記念すべき1曲目を
that memorable first song...
これから披露したいと思います！
...I'd like to perform now!
それでは聞いてください
Now, please listen.
「キミの秒針」
"Your Second Hand"
戻れないからまた
Because I can't go back...
愛おしさが増す
...my affection only grows.
君に 会いたいよ
I want to see you.
君から受け取った
The story I received from you...
壊れそうなストーリー
...that felt so fragile.
どこまでも広がる
Spreading out everywhere...
碧い空
...is the azure sky.
変わらない毎日も
The unchanging days...
色のない夢も
...and the colorless dreams.
手放して 始めようよ
Let's let go and start anew.
不安な夜を数え
Counting the anxious nights...
泣きながら迎えた朝でもいい
...even if it's a morning met with tears.
時計の針のように
Like the hands of a clock...
刻んだ思い出たち 広げた
...I spread out the memories we carved.
戻れないからまた
Because I can't go back...
愛おしさが増す
...my affection only grows.
君に 会いたいよ
I want to see you.
二人で温めた
The precious story...
大切なストーリー
...that we nurtured together.
遠くまで続いた
Stretching far into the distance...
果てない道
...is the endless road.
疲れたら代わるから
"I'll take over if you're tired,"
そう言ってくれた
...you said to me.
優しさに 触れて癒えた
Touching that kindness, I was healed.
受け入れてくれたこと
Accepting me as I am...
忘れない 嬉しくて満ちた日
...I'll never forget those days full of joy.
雨上がる胸に
In my heart after the rain stops...
架かった虹のように
...like a rainbow overhead,
きれいな君からの言葉
...the beautiful words from you,
一つ一つが
each and every one...
今も 宝物
...is still a treasure to me.
支えてくれたから
Because you supported me...
輝ける この気持ち 届けよう
...let me deliver this shining feeling to you.
時計の針のように
Like the hands of a clock...
刻んだ思い出たち 広げた
...I spread out the memories we carved.
戻れないからまた
Because I can't go back...
愛おしさが増す
...my affection only grows.
君に 会いたいよ
I want to see you.
雨上がる胸に
In my heart after the rain stops...
架かった虹のように
...like a rainbow overhead,
きれいな君からの言葉
...the beautiful words from you,
一つ一つが
each and every one...
今も 宝物
...is still a treasure to me.
はい！ということで、みんなどうだったかな？
Alright! So, how was it, everyone?
今回の新曲「キミの秒針」は
My new song this time, "Kimi no Byoushin,"
shidhoの魔王様が作詞、
features lyrics by shidho's Demon Lord,
そして、美明亜津様が作曲、編曲、
and composition and arrangement by Mimegumi Atsu-sama,
そして編曲にはなんと、加藤嵩之様も加わっていただきました！
and for the arrangement, Takayuki Kato-sama even joined us!
いや、今回は
Well, this time,
ボイスドラマ連動企画の第一弾として
as the first part of a voice drama tie-in project,
ストーリー全体のね、テーマソングを担うような、多岐にわたる楽曲に仕上がっております！
it's a multifaceted track serving as the theme song for the whole story!
まぁドラマの鍵となるね、「秒針」というメタファーにも要注目してください！
Please also pay close attention to the "second hand" metaphor, a key to the drama!
shidhoさんだけではなく、この後ね、豪華アーティストの皆様にも
Not just shidho-san, but many other wonderful artists
たくさん書いていただいたので、皆様リリースお楽しみに！
wrote for us afterwards, so please look forward to the release!
こちらの「キミの秒針」は、各音楽サイトは、ちょっと間が空いちゃうんだけど、
"Kimi no Byoushin" will be on various music sites—though there's a bit of a gap—
3月15日の0時から配信予定でございます！
starting at midnight on March 15th!
まぁちょっと公開まで時間が空くから、それまでこの配信、
Since there's some time until the release, until then,
何度も見返してみてくださーい！聴き込んでね！
please watch this stream over and over! Listen to it a lot!
そしてそして、MVもね、ちょっと後日公開なので、
And also, the MV will be released at a later date,
楽しみにしててくださーい！
so please look forward to it!
ということで、今日のちょこの生誕ライブはどうだったかな？
So, how was Choco's birthday live today?
まぁこの後はすぐに、ちょっとね、冒頭最初の方でお披露目した
Well, right after this, as I revealed at the very beginning,
ノエルちゃんとラミィちゃんとの3人の「初恋大戦争」の
the three of us—Noel, Lamy, and I—will have the
MV公開があって、
MV release of "Hatsukoi Daisensou,"
その後、メン限でちょっとライブと撮影会の続きとか
and after that, in the members-only stream, we'll continue with the live and a photo session,
ちょっとね、メン限でしか見れないシチュエーションドラマとかやるので、
and I'll be doing situation dramas that you can only see there,
ぜひぜひ気になる人は見に行ってください！
so if you're interested, please come and watch!
それではまた後でお会いしましょう！
Well then, I'll see you again later!
おつかれーとー、はむっ！
Otsu-kareto, hamu!
出演：癒月ちょこ、白銀ノエル、雪花ラミィ
Cast: Yuzuki Choco, Shirogane Noel, Yukihana Lamy
アキ・ローゼンタール、ロボ子さん、風真いろは、不知火フレア
Aki Rosenthal, Roboco-san, Kazama Iroha, Shiranui Flare
サムネイル：フジモリ / ロゴ：関方あさぎり
Thumbnail: Fujimori / Logo: Sekigata Asagiri
映像制作：Alvitoo20, かねふぉら, 吐水天, Hate, Meira, TARO...
Video Production: Alvitoo20, kanefora, Hate, Meira, TARO...
Direction: SHIG / 振付: FreeM / Music: 合同会社 VESSEL LIFE
Direction: SHIG / Choreography: FreeM / Music: VESSEL LIFE LLC
制作：COVER Corp. STUDIO / SPECIAL THANKS：ちょこめいと
Production: COVER Corp. STUDIO / SPECIAL THANKS: Choco-mate